regus.co.in 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy

## Information about our organization and websites

Regus plc and its subsidiaries (“Regus Group”) are providing this Privacy Policy provides notice to you of our Privacy Policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and revisit this page from time to time to review any changes that may have been made.

Regus Group may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect on the date set out in the posted Privacy Policy, unless otherwise specified.

## Sites covered by this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all Regus owned websites and domains, including [Regus.com](http://www.regus.com/), [HQ.com](http://www.hq.com/), as well as regional or country-specific sites (collectively, “Regus Group Websites”). The Regus Group Websites may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Regus Group Websites. We do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our own privacy practices. This Privacy Policy does not cover any personal data that you choose to give to unrelated third parties. We do not monitor or control the information collected by such sites or the privacy practices of any third parties, and we are not responsible for their practices or the content of their sites.

## Types of information we collect and use

In this policy, “personal information” or “personal data” means information about an identifiable individual that is subject to protection under the law in the jurisdiction in which you reside. In some jurisdictions, “personal information” or “personal data” will not include business contact information.

The Regus Group Website collects information through a variety of different ways and for different purposes. If you choose to register with the Regus Group Websites, then you will be requested to provide contact information (name, address, telephone number, email address, a unique login name, and password). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. We may also use your contact information to send you information about other Regus Group products and services as well as promotional material that may be of interest to you from some of our marketing partners. If you do not want to receive these promotional announcements, you may opt-out when you provide us with contact information or at any time after you register by updating your preferences (see the Opt-Out section below).

You also have the option to provide demographic information (such as type of business, size of business, locations, etc.). Regus Group uses this demographic information to understand your needs and interests and to provide you a more personalized experience on our site. The information is used by Regus Group to process your orders, enable participation in promotions, and facilitate your relationship with us.

Through the Regus Group Websites, you can order products or services, request information, or subscribe to marketing or support materials. In order to purchase a product or service from us, we will request certain information from you. You will need to provide contact information (such as name, email and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, billing address, and expiration date). Financial information collected from you is used only to bill you for the products and services that you have purchased.

If we collect credit card information from you, we only use this information for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit card information and other similar sensitive personal data are not used for any other purpose by Regus Group without your express consent. We do not retain your credit card information after processing a payment unless you grant us permission to retain your credit card information for future purchases.

In most cases, you provide us with your consent to use your personal data in accordance with this policy by providing us with that information. In some cases, we may specifically ask for your express consent if we believe that the information is sensitive or our use of the information may include other uses not covered by this Privacy Policy or another privacy notice to which we have made available to you.

Regus Group Websites automatically collects technical information about your visit (such as browser type, Internet service provider, platform type, internet protocol (IP) addresses, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp). We do not associate this information with other information about you. We aggregate this information for reporting about the Regus Group Websites to analyze trends, diagnose problems with our server and administer the Regus Group Website, to track user movement and use, and to gather broad demographic information.

## Communications from Regus Group

Once you register, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also respond to your inquiries, provide services you request and manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone and will make every effort to honor your preference.

We will also send you information on new products, services, special savings, promotions and general information. If you do not want to re ceive this information, you can opt-out of receiving future mailings (see Opt-Out section below).

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You can sign up for these newsletters from us on our registration page. You may unsubscribe at any time (see Opt-Out section below).

When necessary, Regus Group will send you service-related announcements, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you may deactivate your account with the Regus Group Website.

Please note that we do not provide your email address to our business partners. However, we may send you offers on behalf of our business partners. You can opt out from receiving email offers from Regus Group as described below.

## Sharing of information and Cross-border Transfers

Regus Group contracts with third-party service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions described above. These se rvice providers may change or we may contract with additional service providers to better accommodate our customers. Regus Group affiliates may provide services to you or to your local Regus affiliate and may receive personal data about you. If we transfer your personal data to affiliates or third parties, we require the recipients of your personal data to safeguard your personal data using administrative, technical and security procedures; however, your personal data will also be subject to the laws of the jurisdiction governing our affiliate or the third party.

Your personal data may be transferred across state borders and country borders. Residents of the EEA and Canada should understand that your personal data may be transferred outside of the EEA and Canada to the United States and other countries for the purposes of data consolidation, storage, simplified customer information management, reporting and other internal uses.

Regus Group does not disclose personal data with third parties for their own use without your permission. However, in some cases, Regus Group may be required to share information as a result of applicable law. For example, Regus Group may be required to disclose information as a result of a court order, subpoena or warrant. In addition, we may, subject to applicable law, voluntarily provide information in order to assist in a law enforcement investigation or where the disclosure is necessary to protect our systems, our business or the rights of others.

## Cookies and other digital markers

Regus automatically gather information through the use of cookies and other digital markers. Cookies and digital markers are small computer files that may be stored on your computer’s hard drive or embedded in our website pages that enable us to identify you and track your visit on the Regus Group Website. For example, when you book office space, we use cookies in the checkout process in order to keep track of your order as you move through each step of the booking process. Regus may use the services of third-parties to collect and process personal information through the use of cookies and other digital markers on our behalf. You may disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in the preferences or options menu in your browser. If you choose to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas of the Regus Group Website.

## Children’s privacy

Regus Group is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. Regus Group does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and Regus Group does not target its websites to children under 13.

## Your choices and opting-out

Regus Group gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product-and service-specific information and Regus Group-wide marketing communications. Regus Group-wide communications may include new product information, special offers, or an invitation to participate in market research.Regus Group provides you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personal data used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product from us but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on the order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and/or promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communications or by emailing us at [webmaster@regus.com](mailto:webmaster@regus.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy%20enquiry). Please type “Opt-Out” in the subject-line.

## Access to and accuracy of your information

We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable effort to provide you with online access and the opportunity to change your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to your data. Subject to applicable law, we reserve the right to refuse to provide visitors to our websites with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.

## Keeping your information secure

Regus Group does not guarantee or warrant the security of our servers nor can we guarantee that information you supply through the Regus Group Website will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. We follow generally accepted industry technical standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secured socket layer technology.

## Business transitions

In the event that Regus Group goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred.

## Terms and Conditions

If you choose to visit our Regus Group Websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including, but not limited to, disclaimers of warranty, limitations of liability, and arbitration of disputes.

## Contacting us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or to advise us of a concern relating to the handling of your personal information, please send us an e-mail at [webmaster@regus.com](mailto:webmaster@regus.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy%20enquiry). If your concern is privacy related, please type “Privacy” in the subject-line of your e-mail.

October 21, 2013
